Guide to the William Hewlett Papers M1995
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Financial, 1945-2008
  - Subseries E: Trust Funds and Estate, 1958-2008
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Watts and Whelan, Portfolio Reports, 1995 (Box 388, Folder 2)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Account Register, 1997 (Box 388, Folder 3)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Agency Account, 1995 (Box 388, Folder 4)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Agency Account: Correspondence, 1997 (Box 388, Folder 5)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Agency Account: Correspondence, 1998 (Box 388, Folder 6)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Agency Account: Correspondence, 2000 (Box 388, Folder 7)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Agency Account: Statements, 1997 (Box 389, Folder 1)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Agency Account: Statements, 1998 (Box 389, Folder 2)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Agency Account: Statements, 2000 (Box 389, Folder 3)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Checking Account: Correspondence, 1999 (Box 389, Folder 4)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Checking Account: Correspondence, 2000 (Box 389, Folder 5)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Checking Account: Deposits, 1999 (Box 389, Folder 6)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Checking Account: Deposits, 2000 (Box 389, Folder 7)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Checking Account: Deposits, 2001 (Box 389, Folder 8)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Checking Account: Reconciliations, 1999 (Box 389, Folder 9)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Checking Account: Reconciliations, 2000 (Box 389, Folder 10)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Checking Account: Reconciliations, 2001 (Box 390, Folder 1)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Checking Account: Reconciliations, 2002 (Box 390, Folder 2)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Checking Account: Statements, 1997 (Box 390, Folder 3)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Checking Account: Terms and Conditions, 1999-2001 (Box 390, Folder 4)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account, 1984 (Box 390, Folder 5)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account, 1992 (Box 390, Folder 6)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account, 1994 (Box 390, Folder 7)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account, 1995 (Box 390, Folder 8)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account, 1997 (Box 391, Folder 1)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account, 1998 (Box 391, Folder 2)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account, 2001 (Box 391, Folder 3)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account: Correspondence, 1999 (Box 391, Folder 4)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account: Correspondence, 2000 (Box 391, Folder 5)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account: Correspondence, 2001 (Box 391, Folder 6)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account: Fast-Tax Statements, 1999 (Box 391, Folder 7)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account: Menlo Investment Group (Don Sedam): Correspondence, 2001 (Box 391, Folder 8)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account: Statements, 1999 (Box 392, Folder 1)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Community Property Account: Statements, 2000 (Box 392, Folder 2)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 392, Folder 3)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Custody Account, 1994 (Box 392, Folder 4)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Custody Account, 1997 (Box 392, Folder 5)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Custody Account Fast-Tax Statements, 1999 (Box 392, Folder 6)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Custody Account Statements, 1995 (Box 392, Folder 7)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Custody Account Statements, 1999 (Box 392, Folder 8)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Loan, 1997 (Box 392, Folder 9)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Personal Account, 1996 (Box 392, Folder 10)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Personal Account, 1997 (Box 393, Folder 1)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Rosemary B. Hewlett Account, 1996-1997 (Box 393, Folder 2)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Statements, 1996 (Box 393, Folder 3)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank: Statements, 1999 (Box 393, Folder 4)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank/Technical Trading Corporation (Fred McCahey), 1998 (Box 393, Folder 5)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank/Technical Trading Corporation (Fred McCahey): Agreements, 1994-2002 (Box 393, Folder 6)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank/Technical Trading Corporation (Fred McCahey): Correspondence, 2000 (Box 393, Folder 7)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank/Technical Trading Corporation (Fred McCahey): Fast-Tax Statements, 2000 (Box 393, Folder 8)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank/Technical Trading Corporation (Fred McCahey): Statements, 2000 (Box 393, Folder 9)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank/Technical Trading Corporation (Fred McCahey): Statements, 2000-2001 (Box 394, Folder 1)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Wells Fargo Bank/Technical Trading Corporation (Fred McCahey): Statements, 2002 (Box 394, Folder 2)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Whelan and Gratny Capital Management (Gabe Whelan), 1996 (Box 394, Folder 3)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Whelan and Gratny Capital Management (Gabe Whelan), 1997-1998 (Box 394, Folder 4)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Whelan and Gratny Capital Management (Gabe Whelan): Portfolio Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 394, Folder 5)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Whelan and Gratny Capital Management (Gabe Whelan): Portfolio Reports (part 1 of 2), 1997-1999 (Box 394, Folder 6)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Whelan and Gratny Capital Management (Gabe Whelan): Portfolio Reports (part 2 of 2), 1997-1999 (Box 395, Folder 1)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Whelan and Gratny Capital Management (Gabe Whelan): Statements, 1998-1999 (Box 395, Folder 2)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Whelan and Gratny Capital Management (Gabe Whelan): Statements, 1999-2000 (Box 395, Folder 3)
    - William R. Hewlett Revocable Trust: Will and Codicil to Will of William R. Hewlett, 1988-1995 (Box 395, Folder 4)
    - William R. Hewlett Trusts: 1099 Forms, 1991 (Box 395, Folder 5)
    - William R. Hewlett Trusts: General, 1978-1991 (Box 395, Folder 6)
    - William R. Hewlett Trusts: Portfolio Evaluations, 1983 (Box 395, Folder 7)
    - William R. Hewlett Trusts: Statements, 1983 (Box 395, Folder 8)
    - William R. Hewlett Trusts: Tax Carryforwards, 1989-1998 (Box 395, Folder 9)
  - Subseries F: General, 1952-2001
    The series contains correspondence, statements, bills, and various financial records related to savings, loans, expense accounts, insurance, and other matters related to Hewlett's general finances. In some instances a sample of statements and bills were kept.
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1965-1966 (Box 396, Folder 1)
      This was an account with Hewlett-Packard to cover personal expenses.
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1968-1969 (Box 396, Folder 2)
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1970-1972 (Box 396, Folder 3)
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1973-1975 (Box 396, Folder 4)
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1978-1979 (Box 396, Folder 5)
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1980 (Box 396, Folder 6)
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1981 (Box 396, Folder 7)
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1982 (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1983-1984 (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1987 (Box 397, Folder 3)
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1988 (Box 397, Folder 4)
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1989 (Box 397, Folder 5)
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1990 (Box 397, Folder 6)
    - Account 1212/Account 13, 1991 (Box 397, Folder 7)
    - Account 1213, 1991-1992 (Box 397, Folder 8)
    - Account 1213, 1993 (Box 398, Folder 1)
    - Account 1213, 1995-1996 (Box 398, Folder 2)
    - Bank of California: Correspondence and Statements, 1965-1972 (Box 398, Folder 3)
    - Bank of California: Correspondence and Statements, 1973-1975 (Box 398, Folder 4)
    - Bank of California: Correspondence and Statements, 1979-1982 (Box 398, Folder 5)
    - Bank of California: Correspondence and Statements, 1984-1987 (Box 398, Folder 6)
    - Bank of California: Correspondence and Statements, 1988-1990 (Box 398, Folder 7)
    - Bank of California: Correspondence and Statements, 1991-1994 (Box 398, Folder 8)
    - Bank of California: Joint Account, 1978 (Box 399, Folder 1)
    - Car Phone, 1993-1995 (Box 399, Folder 2)
    - Carol Todd Chronological (part 1 of 6), 2000 (Box 399, Folder 3)
    - Carol Todd Chronological (part 2 of 6), 2000 (Box 399, Folder 4)
    - Carol Todd Chronological (part 3 of 6), 2000 (Box 399, Folder 5)
    - Carol Todd Chronological (part 4 of 6), 2000 (Box 399, Folder 6)
    - Carol Todd Chronological (part 5 of 6), 2000 (Box 399, Folder 7)
    - Carol Todd Chronological (part 6 of 6), 2000 (Box 399, Folder 8)
    - City Center and Federal Savings and Loan Association, 1974-1981 (Box 400, Folder 1)
    - Computers Purchased, 1986-1992 (Box 400, Folder 2)
    - Credit Bureau of Palo Alto, 1995 (Box 400, Folder 3)
    - Credit Cards, 1977 (Box 400, Folder 4)
    - Crocker Bank: Correspondence and Statements, 1965-1972 (Box 400, Folder 5)
    - Crocker Bank: Correspondence and Statements, 1974-1980 (Box 400, Folder 6)
    - Crocker Bank: Correspondence and Statements, 1981-1987 (Box 400, Folder 7)
    - Crocker Bank: Stanford-Joint Accounts, 1984-1987 (Box 400, Folder 8)
    - Crocker-Anglo National Bank: Flat Notes and Statements, 1957-1960 (Box 400, Folder 9)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological, 1986 (Box 400, Folder 10)
      Contains correspondence and records with information on philanthropy, trusts, stocks, properties, San Felipe Ranches, contributions and other financial management. Reagan was a business manager and trust accountant that worked for the Hewlett and Packard families for about a decade.
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological, 1987 (Box 400, Folder 11)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological, 1988 (Box 400, Folder 12)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 1 of 2), 1989 (Box 400, Folder 13)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 2 of 2), 1989 (Box 401, Folder 1)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 1 of 3), 1990 (Box 401, Folder 2)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 2 of 3), 1990 (Box 401, Folder 3)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 3 of 3), 1990 (Box 401, Folder 4)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 1 of 3), 1991 (Box 401, Folder 5)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 2 of 3), 1991 (Box 401, Folder 6)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 3 of 3), 1991 (Box 402, Folder 1)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 1 of 2), 1992 (Box 402, Folder 2)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 2 of 2), 1992 (Box 402, Folder 3)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 1 of 6), 1993 (Box 402, Folder 4)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 2 of 6), 1993 (Box 402, Folder 5)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 3 of 6), 1993 (Box 402, Folder 6)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 4 of 6), 1993 (Box 403, Folder 1)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 5 of 6), 1993 (Box 403, Folder 2)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 6 of 6), 1993 (Box 403, Folder 3)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 1 of 4), 1994 (Box 403, Folder 4)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 2 of 4), 1994 (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 3 of 4), 1994 (Box 403, Folder 6)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 4 of 4), 1994 (Box 403, Folder 7)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 1 of 10), 1995 (Box 404, Folder 1)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 2 of 10), 1995 (Box 404, Folder 2)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 3 of 10), 1995 (Box 404, Folder 3)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 4 of 10), 1995 (Box 404, Folder 4)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 5 of 10), 1995 (Box 404, Folder 5)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 6 of 10), 1995 (Box 404, Folder 6)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 7 of 10), 1995 (Box 404, Folder 7)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 8 of 10), 1995 (Box 405, Folder 1)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 9 of 10), 1995 (Box 405, Folder 2)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 10 of 10), 1995 (Box 405, Folder 3)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 1 of 9), 1996 (Box 405, Folder 4)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 2 of 9), 1996 (Box 405, Folder 5)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 3 of 9), 1996 (Box 405, Folder 6)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 4 of 9), 1996 (Box 405, Folder 7)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 5 of 9), 1996 (Box 406, Folder 1)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 6 of 9), 1996 (Box 406, Folder 2)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 7 of 9), 1996 (Box 406, Folder 3)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 8 of 9), 1996 (Box 406, Folder 4)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 9 of 9), 1996 (Box 406, Folder 5)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 1 of 5), 1997 (Box 406, Folder 6)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 2 of 5), 1997 (Box 406, Folder 7)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 3 of 5), 1997 (Box 407, Folder 1)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 4 of 5), 1997 (Box 407, Folder 2)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 5 of 5), 1997 (Box 407, Folder 3)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 1 of 4), 1998 (Box 407, Folder 4)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 2 of 4), 1998 (Box 407, Folder 5)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 3 of 4), 1998 (Box 408, Folder 1)
    - Deborah S. Reagan Chronological (part 4 of 4), 1998 (Box 408, Folder 2)
    - Domestic Employees, 1956-1993 (Box 408, Folder 3)
    - Donna Terman Chronological (part 1 of 2), 1998 (Box 408, Folder 4)
      Contains correspondence and financial paperwork. Donna Terman was a business manager for Los Trancos Management, LLC and Trust Administrator for the Hewlett family.
    - Donna Terman Chronological (part 2 of 2), 1998 (Box 408, Folder 5)
    - Employee Benefits Summary, 1976-1987 (Box 408, Folder 6)
    - Expense Accounts (Hewlett-Packard), 1961-1965 (Box 408, Folder 7)
      Includes expense reports, itineraries, and correspondence which contain a small amount of information travel, meetings, and activities.
    - Expense Accounts (Hewlett-Packard), 1966-1967 (Box 408, Folder 8)
    - Expense Accounts (Hewlett-Packard), 1967-1969 (Box 409, Folder 1)
    - Expense Accounts (Hewlett-Packard), 1970-1971 (Box 409, Folder 2)
    - Expense Accounts (Hewlett-Packard), 1971-1974 (Box 409, Folder 3)
    - Expense Accounts (Hewlett-Packard), 1977-1980 (Box 409, Folder 4)
    - Funds Transfer Agreement, 1992 (Box 409, Folder 5)
    - Hewlett Family Hawaiian Christmas Trip, 1994-1995 (Box 409, Folder 6)
    - Hewlett-Packard Employees Benefits, 1993 (Box 409, Folder 7)
    - Hewlett-Packard Employees Federal Credit Union: First Credit Card, 1996 (Box 409, Folder 8)
      Includes various financial records and images of Hewlett with employees.
    - Hewlett-Packard Employees Federal Credit Union: Statements and Newsletters, 1970-1979 (Box 409, Folder 9)
    - Hewlett-Packard Employees Federal Credit Union: Statements and Newsletters, 1980-1985 (Box 409, Folder 10)
    - Hewlett-Packard Employees Federal Credit Union: Statements and Newsletters, 1986-1988 (Box 409, Folder 11)
    - Hewlett-Packard Employees Federal Credit Union: Statements and Newsletters, 1989-1991 (Box 409, Folder 12)
    - Hewlett-Packard Employees Retirement Trust, 1958 (Box 410, Folder 1)
    - Hewlett-Packard Equipment for Home Use, 1979-1990 (Box 410, Folder 2)
    - Insurance Policies, 1967 (Box 410, Folder 3)
    - Insurance Policies (part 1 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 410, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Policies (part 2 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 410, Folder 5)
    - Insurance Policies (part 3 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 410, Folder 6)
    - Insurance Policies (part 4 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 410, Folder 7)
    - Insurance Policies (part 5 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 410, Folder 8)
    - Insurance Policies (part 6 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 411, Folder 1)
    - Insurance Policies (part 7 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 411, Folder 2)
    - Insurance Policies (part 8 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 411, Folder 3)
    - Insurance Policies (part 9 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 411, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Policies (part 10 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 411, Folder 5)
    - Insurance Policies (part 11 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 411, Folder 6)
    - Insurance Policies (part 12 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 412, Folder 1)
    - Insurance Policies (part 13 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 412, Folder 2)
    - Insurance Policies (part 14 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 412, Folder 3)
    - Insurance Policies (part 15 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 412, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Policies (part 16 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 412, Folder 5)
    - Insurance Policies (part 17 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 412, Folder 6)
    - Insurance Policies (part 18 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 413, Folder 1)
    - Insurance Policies (part 19 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 413, Folder 2)
    - Insurance Policies (part 20 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 413, Folder 3)
    - Insurance Policies (part 21 of 21), 1974-1990 (Box 413, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Policies (part 1 of 6), 1990-1992 (Box 413, Folder 5)
    - Insurance Policies (part 2 of 6), 1990-1992 (Box 413, Folder 6)
    - Insurance Policies (part 3 of 6), 1990-1992 (Box 414, Folder 1)
    - Insurance Policies (part 4 of 6), 1990-1992 (Box 414, Folder 2)
    - Insurance Policies (part 5 of 6), 1990-1992 (Box 414, Folder 3)
    - Insurance Policies (part 6 of 6), 1990-1992 (Box 414, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Policies (part 1 of 3), 1992-1994 (Box 414, Folder 5)
    - Insurance Policies (part 2 of 3), 1992-1994 (Box 414, Folder 6)
    - Insurance Policies (part 3 of 3), 1992-1994 (Box 415, Folder 1)
    - Insurance Policies (part 1 of 3), 1994-1995 (Box 415, Folder 2)
    - Insurance Policies (part 2 of 3), 1994-1995 (Box 415, Folder 3)
    - Insurance Policies (part 3 of 3), 1994-1995 (Box 415, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Policies (part 1 of 5), 1995-1998 (Box 415, Folder 5)
    - Insurance Policies (part 2 of 5), 1995-1998 (Box 415, Folder 6)
    - Insurance Policies (part 3 of 5), 1995-1998 (Box 416, Folder 1)
    - Insurance Policies (part 4 of 5), 1995-1998 (Box 416, Folder 2)
    - Insurance Policies (part 5 of 5), 1995-1998 (Box 416, Folder 3)
    - Insurance Policies, 2001 (Box 416, Folder 4)
    - Last Wills and Testaments of Friends, 1952 (Box 416, Folder 5)
    - Letter of Credit, Lloyds of London, 1983-1992 (Box 416, Folder 6)
    - Loan Amortization Schedules, 1989-1997 (Box 416, Folder 7)
    - Loan Promissory Notes and Interest, 1986-2001 (Box 417, Folder 1)
    - Loan: Black Group, 1992 (Box 417, Folder 2)
    - Loan: Black Group (part 1 of 2), 1994-1997 (Box 417, Folder 3)
    - Loan: Black Group (part 2 of 2), 1994-1997 (Box 417, Folder 4)
    - Loan: Black Group, 1997-1999 (Box 417, Folder 5)
    - Loan: Bradford Deed of Trust, 1989-1991 (Box 417, Folder 6)
    - Loan: Bradford Demand Note, 1983-1987 (Box 417, Folder 7)
    - Loan: Bradford Family, 1983 (Box 417, Folder 8)
    - Loan: Bradford Family, 1985-1988 (Box 417, Folder 9)
    - Loan: Bradford Family, 1993-1997 (Box 417, Folder 10)
    - Loan: Bradford House Construction (part 1 of 2), 1987 (Box 417, Folder 11)
    - Loan: Bradford House Construction (part 2 of 2), 1987 (Box 418, Folder 1)
    - Loan: Bradford House Construction (part 1 of 2), 1987-1992 (Box 418, Folder 2)
    - Loan: Bradford House Construction (part 2 of 2), 1987-1992 (Box 418, Folder 3)
    - Loan: Burgundy Sale to Haugum (part 1 of 2), 1988-1997 (Box 418, Folder 4)
    - Loan: Burgundy Sale to Haugum (part 2 of 2), 1988-1997 (Box 418, Folder 5)
    - Loan: Clay, 1971-1978 (Box 418, Folder 6)
    - Loan: Crowley Promissory Note, 1989-1996 (Box 418, Folder 7)
    - Loan: EPA Electronics, 1968-1974 (Box 419, Folder 1)
    - Loan: Hall, 1986 (Box 419, Folder 2)
    - Loan: Hewlett Family, 1995-1997 (Box 419, Folder 3)
    - Loan: Kohlhaas, Cord Electric Company (part 1 of 5), 1988-1996 (Box 419, Folder 4)
    - Loan: Kohlhaas, Cord Electric Company (part 2 of 5), 1988-1996 (Box 419, Folder 5)
    - Loan: Kohlhaas, Cord Electric Company (part 3 of 5), 1988-1996 (Box 419, Folder 6)
    - Loan: Kohlhaas, Cord Electric Company (part 4 of 5), 1988-1996 (Box 419, Folder 7)
    - Loan: Kohlhaas, Cord Electric Company (part 5 of 5), 1988-1996 (Box 419, Folder 8)
    - Loan: Kozak, 1994-1997 (Box 419, Folder 9)
    - Loan: Huntsberger (part 1 of 5), 1976-2000 (Box 420, Folder 1)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Access restricted due to sensitive information regarding litigation. Should remain closed to researchers until year 2050.
    - Loan: Huntsberger (part 2 of 5), 1976-2000 (Box 420, Folder 2)
    - Loan: Huntsberger (part 3 of 5), 1976-2000 (Box 420, Folder 3)
    - Loan: Huntsberger (part 4 of 5), 1976-2000 (Box 420, Folder 4)
    - Loan: Huntsberger (part 5 of 5), 1976-2000 (Box 420, Folder 5)
    - Loan: Labarre (part 1 of 5), 1990-1995 (Box 421, Folder 1)
    - Loan: Labarre (part 2 of 5), 1990-1995 (Box 421, Folder 2)
    - Loan: Labarre (part 3 of 5), 1990-1995 (Box 421, Folder 3)
    - Loan: Labarre (part 4 of 5), 1990-1995 (Box 421, Folder 4)
    - Loan: Labarre (part 5 of 5), 1990-1995 (Box 421, Folder 5)
    - Loan: Labarre (part 1 of 2), 1995-1999 (Box 422, Folder 1)
    - Loan: Labarre (part 2 of 2), 1995-1999 (Box 422, Folder 2)
    - Loan: Lacey, 1991-1997 (Box 422, Folder 3)
    - Loan: McCahey, 1994-1995 (Box 422, Folder 4)
    - Loan: Mendoza, 1979-1988 (Box 422, Folder 5)
    - Loan: Miller, 1979-1992 (Box 422, Folder 6)
    - Loan: Miramar Beach Inn, 1989-1995 (Box 422, Folder 7)
    - Loan: Miramar Beach Inn, 1995-1999 (Box 423, Folder 1)
    - Loan: Miramar Beach Inn, Foreclosure, 1989-1992 (Box 423, Folder 2)
    - Loan: Promissory Note, 1990-1991 (Box 423, Folder 3)
    - Loan: Royse, 1968-1969 (Box 423, Folder 4)
    - Loan: Schneider, 1982-1985 (Box 423, Folder 5)
    - Loan: Stratton Wynkoop, 1964-1976 (Box 423, Folder 6)
    - Loan: Van Buijtene, 1986-1993 (Box 423, Folder 7)
    - Loan: Whelan, 1984-1987 (Box 423, Folder 8)
    - Loan: Whelan, 1987-1990 (Box 423, Folder 9)
    - Loan: Whelan, 1990-1997 (Box 423, Folder 10)
    - Maureen Cole Chronological, 1997-1998 (Box 424, Folder 1)